

m.mersimoski1999@gmail.co

#### 

076597008



North Macedonia

#### in

linkedin.com/in/mahirmersimoski-134b361a3

#### **SKILLS**

WordPress

Googling

PHP

UX

Dynamic Content

ReactJS

#### **LANGUAGES**

#### English

Full Professional Proficiency

#### Macedonian

Native or Bilingual Proficiency

#### Albanian

Native or Bilingual Proficiency

#### **INTERESTS**

Developing WordPress websites, web apps, ecommerce and mobile applications (yep its possible)

From time to time i like to code in ReactJS

Redesigning, Updating, Optimizing and making mobile & user friendly Websites.

# Mahir Mersimoski

Cool Software Developer

WordPress enthusiast with over 1.5y experience in building Advanced and Dynamic websites and web apps without single line of code. Professional googler with good sense of humor that does what it takes to satisfy the user experience needs and deliver services on time, i like to code in React from time to time.

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

#### Member

#### digicube North Macedonia

02/2021 - Present

Using their office, working with their partner.

#### **Software Developer**

### Newsroom Technologies AG

02/2021 - Present

Building advanced web sites and web applications with WordPress and React

# WordPress Developer & Community Manager

**Pro Option Trader** 

10/2020 - 01/2021

Social network platform for traders.

## Front-end developer

TSD Foundation

01/2018 - 04/2019

Developing and managing their web sites and applications.

#### **CERTIFICATES**

First Place in a Programming Tournament in Bitola, Macedonia (03/2017 - 03/2017)

Upper Intermediate Diploma for English Language (07/2019 - 08/2019)

#### **PROJECTS**

Event scheduler and membership web app for a huge Swiss dentist association

https://parodontologie.ch/ (the new layout is still in development)

Trading Social Network, FaceBook-like platform for Traders

http://prooptiontrader.com/

Bern Congress Organization - Web application for scheduling live events

https://www.bern-co.com/

Trying to gather all my projects in one place, you can find some on my Github and links below

parodontologie.ch/- https://maksutoska.at/ - https://readwp.com/ - www.captainwords.com - homeworkouts101.com - bonsaialchemist.com - easywaybaby.com - https://kulstudios.com/ - efp.osteology.org - electro-tec-digital.ch - www.vks-fachtagung.ch - https://tcs-livestream.ch/

#### **EDUCATION**

# **Dropout Computer Science and Engineering**UIST Paul the Apostle

08/2019 - 08/2020

Courses

Focused on self teaching instead, couldn't waste 5 years of my life. Ohrid, Macedonia